{"data":[{"question":"She can do it straight away.' '_________'","a":"So can I","b":"Neither can I","c":"Nor do I","d":"So do I","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"He was very ill on Saturday.' '_________'","a":"So was I","b":"So did I","c":"Neither was I","d":"Nor was I","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a positive statement:  so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I haven't finished my lesson.' '_________'","a":"Neither have I","b":"Nor I have","c":"So have I","d":"Neither am I","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I'll probably go swimming tomorrow.' _________","a":"Neither will I","b":"So will I","c":"Nor will I","d":"Neither am I","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To agree with a positive statement: so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I've never been to Japan.' '_________'","a":"Nor did I","b":"Neither do I","c":"Neither have I","d":"So have I","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"She hasn't done it yet.' '_________'","a":"Neither does he","b":"Neither hasn't he","c":"Neither has he","d":"So has he","answer":"3","explain":"\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"We are extremely sorry'. '________'","a":"Neither are we","b":"So do we","c":"So are we","d":"So can we","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a positive statement:  so + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I wouldn't like to miss such a good opportunity.' '_________'","a":"Nor would I","b":"Neither do I","c":"So do I","d":"So would I","answer":"1","explain":"\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun \n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement ","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I can't remember what she said.' '_________'","a":"Nor do","b":"Nor can I","c":"So do I","d":"So can I","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- To agree with a negative statement: nor\/neither + auxiliary\/modal verb + pronoun\n\n- Change the auxiliary verb related to the original statement\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I forgot to ring up my wife.' '_________'","a":"So would I","b":"So did I","c":"Neither did I","d":"Nor did I","answer":"2","explain":"- So + auxiliary verb + S","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}